<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Tokens version="1.0">
	<File path="Classes/AmazonSecurityTokenServiceClient.html">
		
		<Token>
			<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/cl/AmazonSecurityTokenServiceClient</TokenIdentifier>
			<Abstract type="html">&lt;summary&gt;
Interface for accessing AmazonSecurityTokenService.</Abstract>
			<DeclaredIn>AmazonSecurityTokenServiceClient.h</DeclaredIn>
			
			<NodeRef refid="16"/>
		</Token>
		
		
		<Token>
			<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/instm/AmazonSecurityTokenServiceClient/getSessionToken:</TokenIdentifier>
			<Abstract type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The GetSessionToken action returns a set of temporary credentials for an AWS account or IAM user. The credentials
consist of an Access Key ID, a Secret Access Key, and a security token. These credentials are valid for the specified
duration only. The session duration for IAM users can be between one and 36 hours, with a default of 12 hours. The
session duration for AWS account owners is restricted to one hour. Providing the AWS Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)
device serial number and the token code is optional.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
For more information about using GetSessionToken to create temporary credentials, go to  Creating Temporary Credentials
to Enable Access for IAM Users  in &lt;i&gt;Using IAM&lt;/i&gt; .
&lt;/p&gt;</Abstract>
			<DeclaredIn>AmazonSecurityTokenServiceClient.h</DeclaredIn>			
			
	<RelatedTokens>
		<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/cl/SecurityTokenServiceGetSessionTokenRequest</TokenIdentifier>
		<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/cl/SecurityTokenServiceGetSessionTokenResponse</TokenIdentifier>
		
	</RelatedTokens>
	
			<Declaration>- (SecurityTokenServiceGetSessionTokenResponse *)getSessionToken:(SecurityTokenServiceGetSessionTokenRequest *)getSessionTokenRequest</Declaration>
			<Parameters>
				<Parameter>
					<Name>getSessionTokenRequest</Name>
					<Abstract type="html">Container for the necessary parameters to execute the GetSessionToken service method on
AmazonSecurityTokenService.</Abstract>
				</Parameter>
			</Parameters>
			<ReturnValue><Abstract type="html">The response from the GetSessionToken service method, as returned by AmazonSecurityTokenService.</Abstract></ReturnValue>
			<Anchor>//api/name/getSessionToken:</Anchor>
		</Token>
		
		<Token>
			<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/instm/AmazonSecurityTokenServiceClient/getFederationToken:</TokenIdentifier>
			<Abstract type="html">&lt;p&gt;
The GetFederationToken action returns a set of temporary credentials for a federated user with the user name and policy
specified in the request. The credentials consist of an Access Key ID, a Secret Access Key, and a security token.
Credentials created by IAM users are valid for the specified duration, between one and 36 hours; credentials created
using account credentials last one hour.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The federated user who holds these credentials has any permissions allowed by the intersection of the specified policy
and any resource or user policies that apply to the caller of the GetFederationToken API, and any resource policies that
apply to the federated user&apos;s Amazon Resource Name (ARN). For more information about how token permissions work, see  Creating Temporary Credentials to
Enable Access for Federated Users  in &lt;i&gt;Using AWS Identity and Access Management&lt;/i&gt; .
&lt;/p&gt;</Abstract>
			<DeclaredIn>AmazonSecurityTokenServiceClient.h</DeclaredIn>			
			
	<RelatedTokens>
		<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/cl/SecurityTokenServiceGetFederationTokenRequest</TokenIdentifier>
		<TokenIdentifier>//apple_ref/occ/cl/SecurityTokenServiceGetFederationTokenResponse</TokenIdentifier>
		
	</RelatedTokens>
	
			<Declaration>- (SecurityTokenServiceGetFederationTokenResponse *)getFederationToken:(SecurityTokenServiceGetFederationTokenRequest *)getFederationTokenRequest</Declaration>
			<Parameters>
				<Parameter>
					<Name>getFederationTokenRequest</Name>
					<Abstract type="html">Container for the necessary parameters to execute the GetFederationToken service method
on AmazonSecurityTokenService.</Abstract>
				</Parameter>
			</Parameters>
			<ReturnValue><Abstract type="html">The response from the GetFederationToken service method, as returned by AmazonSecurityTokenService.</Abstract></ReturnValue>
			<Anchor>//api/name/getFederationToken:</Anchor>
		</Token>
		
	</File>
</Tokens>